healthbuy.com 2018-10-22

# Health & Beauty

Terms and Conditions

This Agreement is between Company and you ("you" or "Customer") This Section sets forth the terms and conditions which apply to the use by you of the Company Sites (as defined below) and any other subscription product or service offered for sale by Company and/or its affiliates (collectively, "Company "). The right to use any product or service offered by Company is personal to you and is not transferable to any other person or entity. Company reserves the right to make changes to the Company sites, policies, and these Terms at any time without notice. 

**1\. Use of the Company Sites.  
**The Company Sites contain links to other Web sites, resources and advertisers. Company is not responsible for the availability of these external sites nor does it endorse or is it responsible for the contents, advertising, products or other materials made available on or through such external sites. Under no circumstances shall Company be held responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any loss or damage caused or alleged to have been caused to a user in connection with the use of or reliance on any content, goods or services available on such external site. You should direct any concerns to such external site's administrator or webmaster.

**2\. Disclaimer of Warranty; Limitation of Liability**  
Company neither endorses nor is responsible for the accuracy or reliability of any opinion, advice or statement on the Company sites, nor for any offensive, defamatory or obscene posting made by. Under no circumstances will Company be liable for any loss or damage caused by your reliance on information obtained through the content on the Company sites. It is your responsibility to evaluate the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of any information, opinion, advice or other content available through the Company sites. Please seek the advice of professionals, as appropriate, regarding the evaluation of any specific information, opinion, advice or other content, including but not limited to financial, health, or lifestyle information, opinion, advice or other content.

**3\. Indemnification.**  
You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Company, its affiliates and their respective directors, officers, employees and agents from and against all claims and expenses, including attorneys' fees, arising out of the use by you of the Company Sites, including claims by other users of your equipment, access, products or membership.

**4\. Shipping.**  
Our standard ground shipping takes from 5 to 10 business days within the continental United States. For international orders, we ship via Federal Express. Generally international shipments take 14-21 business days from day of shipment unless customs causes a delay for some reason.

If you have not received your order within 21 days from your purchase date, please click on the link below visit our online customer care section to request a reshipment of your order.

If you entered the wrong address on our order form and we are forced to reship your package, there will be an additional shipping and handling charge equal to your original order.

To check the status of your order, update your mailing address or request reshipment because you never received your product, [Click Here to Manage your Order](http://www.websupportcenter.com/)

**5\. Sales and Distribution.**  
Distributor will not sell any product on eBay, Amazon, any of their affiliate's websites or any other auction website or online marketplace. Prices do not include and are net of any foreign or domestic governmental taxes or charges of any kind that may be applicable to the sale, licensing, marketing or distribution of the products. Distributor understands and acknowledges that all sales are final and that they are not entitled to return any product for a refund. will not be responsible for any delays or lack of delivery due to customs clearance issues.

**6\. Cancellation Policy.**  
Once an order has been submitted your credit card will be charged. Our ordering process is streamlined so your order will immediately be sent to processing and then shipping. Due to the high volume of orders we receive we will be unable to cancel an order after submitted. Please order carefully.

**7\. 90 Day Return Policy:**   

We take great pride in the superior quality of our products and want you to be pleased with your purchase. We believe in offering the very best value, quality and selection to our customers. You may return any unused and unopened item purchased from us for any reason within Ninety (90) days of your purchase. If you purchased your merchandise through a "Buy Three, Get Three Free" or similar offer, all items must be returned in order to receive a refund. If you return a partial amount of merchandise, you will forfeit the free product and receive a refund on the discount price per item based on the total purchase.

Your complete satisfaction is our ultimate goal. You may return any item shipped by Company, keeping the following in mind:

  * You should return the item to us within 90 days of your purchase date.
  * We do not accept items back that have been opened or used. Opened Items are Non Refundable.
  * Shipping and Handling Fees are Non Refundable.
  * **There is a $10.00 restocking fee for returns.**

To request a refund you must obtain an RMA (Return Authorization). Requests must be made online and submitted with your order information and explanation of the why you wish to return the product. Please do not call for an RMA. If you return your product without a RMA number you will not be refunded. Shipping and handling charges are non-refundable. For returns via mail, you must carefully package the product, you are responsible for the cost of return shipping, and we must physically receive the return within the 90 day period. Company reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to reject any return that does not comply with these requirements. Once your return has been received, a credit to your card or refund check will be issued and an e-mail confirmation will be sent within 30 days.

*Refund Processing and Restocking Fee: $10 Per item e.g. 1 bottle return = $10 Fee. 2 bottle return - $20 Fee. 

**8\. Paid Offers:**   
On paid offers there is no continuity charges and you will only be billed once for your purchase. For example if you buy 1 bottle of dietrine you will be charged $39.95 plus shipping & handling. 

**9\. Unlimited Refill Program Terms: * NO Monthly Charges * NO Auto-Shipping **   

This offer will allow you to order the product every 30 days and pay only $16.97 shipping included on a monthly basis month after month via our automated [order management system](http://www.websupportcenter.com/) by request only. Once your original purchase supply has been depleted, you will be able to request additional supplies every thirty days. If you choose to return your original purchase for any reason, your enrollment to our membership program will be forfeited. Customers will be given a 3-month notice of product cancellation. Unlimited Supplies subject to availability.

**10\. Manufacturer Coupon Offer Terms:**   

Try product for 30 days. If you are not completely satisfied for any reason, you can return it for a refund. Starting 30 days from your order date, you can request a new 30-day supply for FREE every month and only pay $14.97 s/p. For coupon eligibility, simply collect four refills & complete coupon form at [http://www.websupportcenter.com](http://www.websupportcenter.com/downloads/coupon-form.pdf)

**11\. Collection Efforts:**

You understand that Discount Rewards is a monthly-billed continuity program, and a monthly payment obligation for you. Should Discount Rewards be unable to successfully process your payment for a given month of program benefit eligibility, you understand and acknowledge that, if your payment has not been processed for more than fifteen (15) days, Discount Rewards shall be entitled to seek collection of the unpaid funds using either internal or third party collection efforts. You understand and agree that, should Discount Rewards seek collection of unpaid funds as prescribed herein, that Discount Rewards shall be entitled to assess a twenty dollar ($20.00) penalty to re-coup the cost of collection efforts on your account. You further understand and agree that non-payment of a validated payment obligation may entitle Discount Rewards to report the matter to credit agencies, which may negatively impact your credit score. 

**12\. Collection Policy:**

If I enroll in the membership or auto ship ("trial") program today, I am agreeing to be charged the trial amount advertised today and the retail amount advertised when the advertised trial period is over in for my trial product received. If I do not call to cancel the membership or auto ship during the trial period advertised, I am agreeing to pay the retail amount advertised for the trial product received, at the end of the advertised trial period. If the card on file does NOT successfully authorize for that agreed upon retail amount and you have not called to cancel, the company shall be entitled to seek collection of the unpaid funds using either internal or third party collection efforts plus all costs of collection including reasonable interest, reasonable attorney's fees (if suit is filed) and reasonable collection agency fees, including but not limited to late collection fees of $20.00..

**Legal Disclaimer  
**Statements made by Company have not been evaluated by the food and drug administration. The FDA Dose not evaluate or test herbs. These products are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any illness or disease. Consult with your physician for diagnosis or treatment. Use herbs as per instructions and always watch for any allergic reactions. 

The information presented on this site is not presented with the intention of diagnosing any disease or condition or prescribing any treatment. It is offered as information only, for use in the maintenance and promotion of good health in cooperation with a licensed medical practitioner. 

In the event that any individual should use the information presented on this website without a licensed medical practitioner's approval, that individual will be diagnosing for him or herself.

No responsibility is assumed by the author, publisher or distributors of this information should the information be used in place of a licensed medical practitioner's services. No guarantees of any kind are made for the performance or effectiveness of the preparations mentioned on this website. Furthermore, this information is based solely on the traditional and historic use of a given herb, or on clinical trials that are generally not recognized by any US government agency or medical organization. 

This information has not been evaluated by the US Food and Drug Administration, nor has it gone through the rigorous double-blind studies required before a particular product can be deemed truly beneficial or potentially dangerous and prescribed in the treatment of any condition or disease. 

Herbal Safety Guidelines

Before using an herb you are unfamiliar with, find out its medicinal properties. Research it thoroughly and/or consult with an appropriately qualified practitioner or expert. If you are taking prescription drugs, or have a medical condition check with an appropriately qualified practitioner before using herbs medicinally. Herbs have shown overwhelming evidence that they work. Just because a small amount works well does NOT mean that more is better. As individuals we all have different constitutions, sensitivities, allergic reactions and possible health conditions. The following are merely guidelines. They include herbs offered on our websites. This list does not help with administering information on possible interactions and contraindications with prescription medicine. This needs to be discussed with your physician.

**Should I check with my doctor or healthcare provider before using a supplement?**  
This is a good idea, especially for certain population groups. Dietary supplements may not be risk-free under certain circumstances. If you are pregnant, nursing a baby, or have a chronic medical condition, such as, diabetes, hypertension or heart disease, be sure to consult your doctor or pharmacist before purchasing or taking any supplement. While vitamin and mineral supplements are widely used and generally considered safe, you may wish to check with your doctor or pharmacist before taking these or any other dietary supplements. If you plan to use a dietary supplement in place of drugs or in combination with any drug, tell your health care provider first. Many supplements contain active ingredients that have strong biological effects and their safety is not always assured in all users. If you have certain health conditions and take these products, you may be placing yourself at risk.

**Some supplements may interact with prescription and over-the-counter medicines.**  
Taking a combination of supplements or using these products together with medications (whether prescription or OTC drugs) could under certain circumstances produce adverse effects. Be alert to advisories about these products, whether taken alone or in combination. For example: Coumadin (a prescription medicine), ginkgo biloba (an herbal supplement), aspirin (an OTC drug) and vitamin E (a vitamin supplement) can each thin the blood, and taking any of these products together can increase the potential for internal bleeding.

**Some supplements can have unwated effects during surgery.**  
It is important to fully inform your doctor about the vitamins, minerals, herbals or any other supplements you are taking, especially before elective surgery. You may be asked to stop taking these products at least 2-3 weeks ahead of the procedure to avoid potentially dangerous supplement/drug interactions -- such as changes in heart rate, blood pressure and increased bleeding - that could adversely affect the outcome of your surgery.

**Not to be used during pregnancy, or if you are nursing:**  
Alkanet, Aloe, Angelica, Anise, Anise Star, Arnica, Ashwaganda, Barley Grass, Barberry, Basil, Bitter Melon, Black Cohosh, Bladderwrack, Blessed Thistle, Blood Root, Blue Cohosh, Blue Flag, Blue Vervain, Borage, Buckthorn, California Poppy, Cascara Sagrada, Catnip, Celandine, Celery, Chervil, Cinnamon, Club Moss, Comfrey, Coltsfoot, Cubeb, Dong Quai, Elecampane, Ephedra, False Unicorn, Fenugreek, Feverfew, Ginger, Golden Seal, Gravel, Guarana, Gymnema, Horehound, Horsetail, Hyssop, Juniper, Lemongrass, Licorice, Lobelia, Lovage, Lungwort, Mace, Motherwort, Mugwort, Muira Puama, Myrrh, Neem, Oregon Grape, Osha, Parsley, Pennyroyal, Pleurisy, Prickly Ash, Red Clover, Rhodiola, Rosemary, Rue, Sage, Sassafras, Sarsaparilla, Senna, Shepherds Purse, Spikenard, Turkey Rhubarb, Turmeric, Uva Ursi, Vitex, Watercress, White Sage, Wormwood, Yarrow

**Not for persons with history of kidney stones, liver disorders, renal dysfunction or inflammation.**  
Cubeb, Essiac, Horsetail, Hydrangea, Juniper Berries, Kava Kava, Parsley Root, Pennyroyal, Sheep Sorrel, Shepherds Purse, Suma, Sumac, Uva Ursi, Yellowdock, Yohimbe

**Not recommended for person currently taking blood thinning medications:**  
Alfalfa, Angelica, Cramp Bark, Cubeb, Dong Quai, Ginkgo, Meadowsweet, Red Clover, Sarsaparilla, Yohimbe

**Not for persons with stomach inflammation/ulcers serious digestion and/or liver problems. May cause gastrointestinal upset:**  
Black Haw, Blue Flag, Chaparral, Club Moss, Crampbark, Devils Claw, Eucalyptus, Elecampane, Essiac, Gentian, Ginger, Licorice, Lobelia, Parsley Root, Pleurisy, Pygeum, Solomans Seal, Tribulus, Turmeric, Yohimbe

**Not for long-term use:**  
Bilberry Leaf, Black Walnut, Blessed thistle, Borage, Cascara Sagrada, Comfrey, Coltsfoot, Chaparral, Elecampane, Ephedra, Flax, Horsetail, Gentian, Goldenseal, Guarana, Juniper berries, Licorice, Lobelia, Lungwort, Mullein, Nettle Root, Rhubarb, Sage, Sassafras, Sarsaparilla, Senna, Sheep Sorrel, Wild Cherry, Wormwood, Uva Ursi, Yohimbe

**To be used only under the supervision of an expert qualified in the appropriate use of this substance:**  
Calamus, Horse Chestnut, Lobelia, Licorice, Mandrake, Poke, Tonka

Do not use if you have abdominal pain or diarrhea, discontinue if these occur. Consult health practitioner prior to use if pregnant, nursing, and taking medication or have a medical condition. Do not exceed recommended dose. Not for long term use:   
Aloe, Buckthorn, Cascara Sagrada, Senna, Turkey Rhubarb, Yohimbe

**May cause photo toxicity in some individuals at high dosage. Avoid long exposure to sun if using internally:**  
Angelica, Celery Seed, Orange Peel, Rue, St. Johns Wort

Seek advice from health practitioner prior to use if pregnant, nursing, have high blood pressure, heart or thyroid disease, diabetes, difficulty in urination due to prostate enlargement, or if taking mao inhibitor or other prescription drug. Reduce/discontinue use if nervousness, tremor, sleeplessness, loss of appetite or nausea occur. Do not exceed recommended dose. Keep out of reach of children:  
Ephedra, st. Johns wort, yohimbe

**Seek advice from a health practitioner before use if you have/may have had kidney or liver disease. Discontinue use if nausea, fever, fatigue or jaundice (dark urine, yellow discoloration of eyes) should occur:**

**Boldo, Chaparral**

Statements made by Company have not been evaluated by the food and drug administration. The FDA Does not evaluate or test herbs. These products are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any illness or disease. Consult with your physician for diagnosis or treatment. Use herbs as per instructions and always watch for any allergic reactions. 

Privacy Policy

Last Updated on May 25, 2018

We (and our affiliates) are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to all our websites ("Websites") and our services ("Service").

This Privacy Policy governs our data collection, processing and usage practices. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information. If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Websites or the Service.

We periodically update this Privacy Policy. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice by sending you an email notification.

While we will notify you of any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically.

  1. Information we collect about you
  2. How and why we use your personal data
  3. How we use your personal data for marketing
  4. How we share your data with third parties
  5. How we protect your data
  6. How long we keep your personal data
  7. Your rights
  8. Contact us
  9. Cookies

#### 1\. Information we collect about you

Personal and contact information including your name, age, telephone number, postal address, email address, username and social media username(s). We may collect some of that contact information when you interact with us including via our Customer Care Team.

Details (and copies) of your communications and interactions with us via our Customer Care Team or otherwise, including by email, telephone (voice recordings), post and online via webchat, the feedback button or on social media channels.

Copies of documents you provide to prove your identity (including driving license and passport) when there is a legal reason to request this from you.

Transaction details including payments from you for subscription or purchase of the Service.

Your financial information including your payment card information when you make a purchase or subscribe to the Service.

Information about how you use our Websites, and which websites you came to us from.

Technical information about your device or browser when you use our Websites, including geolocation data to determine what country you are accessing our Websites from, your internet protocol (IP) address, device ID, browser type and version and time zone setting, which may in some circumstances be personal data.

We may also receive personal data directly from you or from various third parties and public sources, including from social media channels (if you interact with us through those channels), or other third parties.

#### 2\. How and why we use your personal data

Below, we set out all of the ways we use your personal data, and why. We have also identified what our legitimate interests are where appropriate. 

It is sometimes necessary for us to process your personal data in order to enter into a contract with you, or to satisfy a contractual requirement (referred to as "performance of a contract with you" below), or to comply with a statutory requirement. In those circumstances, if you do not provide the personal data we require, we will be unable to provide our services to you. 

_Registration_

| How:| We use your personal and contact information to register you as a new customer/client. We collect financial information if you register payment card information when purchasing or subscribing to one of our services.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for the performance of a contract with you.  
  
_Accessing Website content_

How:| We use the personal and contact information provided by you and the transaction details about your purchases, to provide our services to you.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for the performance of a contract with you.  
  
_Managing your account_

How:| We use your personal and contact information, financial information, and transaction details about your purchases, to manage your account.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for the performance of a contract with you.  
  
_Communicating with you_

How:| We use the personal and contact information provided by you, copies of your communications with us and, in some circumstances, transaction details, to manage our relationship with you. For example: 

  * to notify you about changes to our Account Terms or Privacy Policy;
  * to communicate with you in response to any query, request or complaint you may have including by email, telephone and in web chat whether relating to any services that you have purchased from us or otherwise.

---|---  
Why:| Necessary for the performance of a contract with you.  
Necessary to comply with a legal obligation.  
Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated and to study the services we provide).  
  
_Staff training_

How:| We may use copies of your communications with us (including voice recordings) in order to train our staff.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to ensure that we are able to provide the best service to you).  
  
_Market research_

How:| We may use the personal and contact information you have provided to ask you to take part in market research or a survey. We also use the results of any surveys or market research that you undertake to improve our Websites and services.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to assess and improve our services and business).  
  
_Technical issues_

How:| If you contact us about an issue, we may use technical information, and personal and contact information to administer and protect our business and Website (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data).  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for our legitimate interests (for providing our services, the provision of administration and IT services, security and fraud prevention). Necessary to comply with a legal obligation.  
  
_Experience_

How:| We use information about your use of our Websites, together with technical information about your device and (in some circumstances) your personal and contact information, and other relevant information that we receive from you or third parties (including aggregated information that we combine with your personal data), to deliver relevant website content and other marketing to you, and to manage the delivery of that content. For example, we may automatically display relevant advertisements to you based on your use of our Websites.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to ensure that you are shown relevant content based on your use of our Websites).  
  
_Advertising effectiveness_

How:| We use information about your use of our Websites and, in some circumstances, personal and contact information about you, to measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to determine how effective advertising is in order to improve advertising, its relevance and in order to fulfil contracts we have with our marketing partners).  
  
_Analytics_

How:| We use information about your use of our Websites and technical information, including about your device or where you are accessing our Websites from, to optimize our service and to improve our app, Website, services, direct marketing, student relationships, behavior profiling and experiences.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to measure the interactions with our Websites, to keep our Websites updated and relevant, to develop our business and to improve our marketing strategy).  
  
_Publicity_

How:| We may use your personal and limited contact information in any publicity materials provided that you have given your consent.   
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to develop our business and to improve our marketing strategy).  
  
_Regulatory compliance_

How:| We may use your personal and contact information, financial information, information about any transaction between you and us, information about your use of our Websites, or technical information, to enable us to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary to comply with a legal obligation.  
  
_Fraud prevention_

How:| We may use your personal and contact information, financial information, information about any transaction between you and us, information about your use of our Websites, or technical information, in order to undertake analysis for the purposes of identifying and dealing with any fraud or fraudulent activity.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary to comply with a legal obligation. Necessary for our legitimate interests (to ensure that transactions and interactions with us are not fraudulent).  
  
_Queries_

How:| We may use your personal and contact information, financial information, information about any transaction between you and us, information about your use of our Websites, or technical information for the purpose of dealing with any request, complaint or query from you.  
---|---  
Why:|  Necessary to comply with a legal obligation. Necessary for our legitimate interests (to respond to you and to deal with any request you may have).  
  
We use your personal data to create aggregated data sets. You are not identifiable from that aggregated data and it is not considered personal data.

However, if we combine or connect aggregated data with your personal data so that it can directly or indirectly identify you, we treat the combined data as personal data which will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

#### 3\. How we use your personal data for marketing

We send you marketing communications through a number of different channels. You may receive newsletters, email notifications and other marketing communications that either you request from us or which you consent to by opting in when completing a registration form on our service., and/or have not asked us to stop sending marketing by email to you.

How to opt out of this marketing

You may opt out from receiving such marketing communications and notifications from us at any time. There are several ways you can do this. To stop receiving marketing by email, either:

  * Click "unsubscribe" or update preferences in any email communication we send;
  * Contact us in writing; or
  * Email us at domainadmincontact@gmail.com.

#### 4\. How we share your data with third parties

We sometimes share the data we collect from you with the following trusted third parties:

  * Banks and payment providers - to set up and/or to obtain payment of any amounts due to us.
  * Our IT system providers - in order to provide software to set up your account, to communicate with you via webchat and other communications providers and to provide our systems to us, including for the purposes of hosting, support and software licensing.
  * Social media platforms - for the purpose of fulfilling the service and targeted advertising.
  * Online survey companies and market research agencies - to undertake surveys (including for example, our Websites satisfaction survey) and other market research and to analyze the results.
  * Digital analytics companies - for the purposes of website analytics and reporting in respect of our analytics and marketing.
  * Professional advisers including lawyers, bankers, auditors and insurers - for the purposes of providing consultancy, banking, legal, insurance and accounting services.
  * Police or other such regulatory authority - as part of an investigation or otherwise for legal or regulatory purposes.
  * Auditors - to audit our systems and transactions for the purposes of ensuring efficiency, or regulatory or contractual compliance.
  * We will disclose your personal information to third parties if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal or regulatory obligation or request. We do this in order to protect our rights, property or safety or of our clients, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection.

How to opt out of this marketing

You may opt out from receiving such marketing communications and notifications from us at any time. There are several ways you can do this. To stop receiving marketing by email, either:

  * Click "unsubscribe" or update preferences in any email communication we send;
  * Contact us in writing; or
  * Email us at domainadmincontact@gmail.com.

#### 5\. How we protect your data

We have put various measures in place to protect your personal data:

  * All of your shopping cart checkout information is processed on our secure servers. You can see this via the https:// in the url as well as your browser showing the site listed as "Secure" in the address bar. This means that all of the data is encrypted while it is being transmitted for security purposes.
  * When your data is received and processed, it is stored on secured servers with restricted access with all necessary and reasonable safeguards put in place to protect said information.
  * In some cases, we may disclose your personal data to third parties. If and when we do so, we make every effort to ensure the third party takes all necessary steps to secure the information and protect your data. However, in some cases we may be required by law to disclose your information to a third party and may not always have control over how that information is secured.
  * Your personal data may be processed by our staff or one of the referenced third parties. At such times only the minimum amount of data needed to perform their given duties is accessed. Such staff may exist outside of the EEA (European Economic Area.)

#### 6\. How long we keep your personal data

We will only keep your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

At the end of that retention period, your data will either be deleted or anonymized (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

In some circumstances, you may be entitled to ask us to delete your data: see "Your rights" below for further information.

#### 7\. Your rights

You have the right:

  * to ask us not to use your personal data for marketing;
  * to ask us not to process your personal data where it is processed on the basis of legitimate interests, if there are no compelling reasons for that processing;
  * to request from us access to personal information held about you (see below);
  * to ask for the information we hold about you to be rectified if it is inaccurate or incomplete;
  * to ask that we stop any consent-based processing of your personal data after you withdraw that consent;
  * to ask, in certain circumstances, to delete the personal data we hold about you;
  * to ask, in certain circumstances, for the processing of that information to be restricted; and
  * to ask, in certain circumstances, for data portability.

#### 8\. Contact us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, including any requests to exercise your rights, please contact the Data Protection Officer at domainadmincontact@gmail.com.

In order to request a copy of the personal data that we hold about you, please send your request in writing to the Data Protection Officer at the above address. To enable us to verify your identity and process your request, you must include all of the following information and documentation with your request:

  * your full name;
  * the email address registered to your account;
  * a description of the data that you are requesting, including a date range;
  * proof of your ID;
  * the date of the request.

If you are unhappy with our processing of your personal data, you have the right to complain at any time. We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with any concerns before you approach the appropriate authority, so please contact the Data Protection Officer by email in the first instance.

#### 9\. Cookies

We use cookies and similar technologies to recognize you, your browser and your device. We also allow carefully selected third parties to use cookies, pixels and ad tags while you are browsing our Websites. These collect information about your browsing habits and usage and allow us to show you ads while you are browsing our Websites and other sites on the internet. All of our advertising cookies used are described in the cookie list below.

There are four main types of cookies and technology. Here's how and why we use them:

_Strictly necessary cookies_

These are cookies that are required for the operation of our Websites. Without these cookies, you will not be able to use some functionality on our Websites, such as signing into your account.

_Performance cookies_

These cookies collect information about how you use our Websites and help us improve the way our Websites work by making it easier for you to navigate to and complete various tasks.

_Functionality cookies_

These cookies allow us to identify whether you are logged into your Figure Eight Training portal and to remember choices you make and your preferences, in order to improve your experience of our Websites.

_Advertising cookies and pixels_

Our carefully selected media partners place third party cookies, pixels and ad tags onto our Websites on our behalf. These cookies record your visit to our Websites, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed.

We use this information to make our Websites, and the content displayed on them, more relevant to you. They are also used to limit the number of times you see certain content, as well to measure the effectiveness of our digital campaigns.

We may share this analytics information with third parties for these purposes. You can delete these cookies and still continue to use our Websites.

More information about these types of cookies and opt out information can be found in Manage your cookies.

_Managing your cookies_

For more information about cookies, how to opt out and the steps you can take to protect your privacy on the internet, go tohttp://www.youronlinechoices.com- the guide to online behavioral advertising and privacy. This website is operated by the Internet Advertising Bureau, the industry body for online advertising. On here you'll find information about how behavioral advertising works, how to opt out, further information about cookies and the steps you can take to protect your privacy on the internet.

If you'd prefer to restrict, block or delete cookies from our Websites, you can do so in your browser settings. If you choose to disable cookies, then please note that this may limit the way you use our Websites. For example, you may have to re-enter information that would have ordinarily been stored as a cookie.

_How to control cookies on your desktop_

_How to control cookies on your mobile device_

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Any changes that we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on our Websites. Where appropriate, we will notify you of the changes periodically.

Copyright 2018 | Last Updated on May 25, 2018 | All Rights Reserved
